imobie.com 2019-09-17

# iMobie - Privacy Policy

iMobie is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We want you to feel secure when visiting our website, using our products and providing information to us. iMobie will only gather your personal information with your consent and for legal purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

This privacy policy has been prepared to inform you of the information we gather and how we use it. This privacy policy applies to all of iMobie’s websites, products, services that display or link to this privacy policy.

#### What information we collect and how we use your information:

Generally, you may visit our websites without providing any personal information or identifying yourself. When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is only used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you. You may also be asked to provide or may provide additional personal data in course of communicating with us about your order, downloading and installing our software, applications and updates, supplying feedback and information about your use of our products or requesting us to stay in touch with you. In certain instances, we may make your information available to partners that are providing services on our behalf. iMobie will only provide those partners with information that is necessary for them to perform the services and who have agreed to take measures to protect your information that are at least as stringent as the measures that we take ourselves. If at any time you tell us that you no longer wish to receive these communications, they will be halted promptly. To comply with applicable laws or respond to valid legal procedures, we may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government agencies.

#### How the third party credit card processors protect customer's information:

iMobie uses secure server hosted by cleverbridge and other third party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

#### Use of cookies:

iMobie uses cookies (small amounts of data stored by your Web browser on your hard drive) to help enable us to offer you more personalized and user-friendly content and service. These cookies, which may be offered by third parties, also allow iMobie to track usage patterns and allow us to continuously improve and manage our website and deliver content that is specific to your interests. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. 

Most Web browsers accept cookies by default, but if you choose not to accept them, you can simply change your browser settings to disable it. If you decline to accept cookies, you may not receive the full benefits that our website has to offer. Here are some guides on how to delete or disable cookies on your browser:   
for Safari users: [how to delete and disable on Safari](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265)  
for Chrome users: [how to delete and disable on Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647)  
for IE users: [how to delete and disable on Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies)  
for Firefox users: [how to delete and disable on Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)  
for Opera users: [how to delete and disable on Opera](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/)  
for Edge users: [how to delete and disable on Microsoft Edge](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy)

#### How we protect your personal information:

iMobie strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choice for its intended use. We apply suitable physical, electronic and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure, misuse, modification, damage or loss.

#### Updates to this privacy policy:

iMobie may update or modify this privacy policy from time to time without prior notice to you, and each such update or modification becomes applicable immediately upon publication. Please review this page often so that you can be aware of our latest policies on privacy and collection of personal information. Your continued use and visitation of the iMobie websites constitutes your consent to the provisions of our privacy policy, as amended from time to time.

This privacy policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.

#### Contact iMobie:

If after reading this statement, you have any questions about iMobie’s privacy policy, please submit your questions to   
[contact@imobie.com](mailto:contact@imobie.com).
